Contact

Bình Tân, HCM 0938074106 (Mobile) nqt99design@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/wagtrung (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Teamwork

User Interaction

Figma

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

IELTS

Honors-Awards

[2022] The Official Logo for the 50th years of UK - Viet Nam diplomatic relations

[2022] The Official Logo for the 30th years of Korea - Vietnam diplomatic relations

[2021] IELTS Tinder Application (cuộc thi Sinh viên với quyền sở hữu trí tuệ S&IP do Cục Sở hữu Trí tuệ và ĐHQG-HCM tổ chức)

[2021] Inspirational Award Key Visual in VFCD2021 by RMIT University (Vietnamese Festival of Creativity and Design)

[2021] The Best Visual Concept in ASUS Zenbook "Hanh trình 10 năm"

Ngo Quang Trung

UX Designer | Product Designer | UI/UX design HCM Vietnam Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

As an Interface Enthusiast and Opportunity seeker, I always gravitate towards UCD (User-Centered Design).

Besides, I am also an active person for challenging myself in lots of creative contests to gain more experiences and connect with people having the same passion in Art and Technology.

When oriented as a UI/UX designer, I have a background in technology and the ability to program web applications from which I understand the feasibility of putting design into practice.

#Drop me a line: nqt99designs@gmail.com

Experience

99designs

Branding Designer

February 2017 - Present (5 years 11 months)

United States

Win 30+ worldwide logo design contests

Design and redesign brand identity

Understand and analyze client briefs and the requirements

Make brand guidelines and other social media packages for the company campaigns

Design everything related to advertising including mockups, banners, and posters for advertising

Adjust and modify the designs following client requests

Communicate in English throughout the 99d platform

MeU Solutions

UI/UX Designer
June 2020 - September 2020 (4 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Produce aesthetically rich UI designs with Figma in HR ERP System Develop wireframes and prototypes

Page 1 of 2

Corporate with team leader and successfully create personas through user research and data

Conduct usability testing and prepare user flows and evaluate its success and risk

Education

International University - VNU HCMC
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Vietnam National University, HCMC